thrivesolo.com 2012-12-22

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY
POLICY

PRIVACY AT SOLO                                                     SAFETY PRECAUTIONS
Solo attaches great importance to handling your data in a secure    Your Solo.account is password protected to prevent others
and private way. Personal data is saved, processed and analyzed     from getting access to your data. We advise you to chose a
only if necessary. Data will not be handed over to third parties    secure password (more than six characters, including
other than for payment issues. Under no circumstances will we       numbers) as well as to change your password periodically.
sell or lease your data. There may be times we use your data
                                                                    When using Solo over a public network, at internet cafes,
anonamously combined with other users data i.e. Solo users
                                                                    or when you are sharing your computer with other people.
have billed £200,000 this month.
                                                                    Log out when you’re done, and shut down the browser window
To improve our service on an ongoing basis, we will evaluate        to make sure others can not access your personal information.
some of the key figures of your account for statistical reasons.
This includes the number of time entries, hours, customers,         CHANGES
projects, services, users and logins.
                                                                    Please note that this privacy policy may change from time to
                                                                    time. We will not reduce your rights under this privacy policy
PERSONAL INFORMATION                                                without telling you about it via e-mail, and we expect that most
When you sign up for an account, you will have to provide some      changes will be minor. You will find the current version right here.
personal information. During the trial period this includes
your name, the name of your account, and your e-mail address.       MORE INFORMATION
To continue using Solo after the trial period, you will have to
                                                                    Please drop us a line if you have any further questions about the
provide your postal address as well.
                                                                    processing or storage of your data.
If you contact Solo via e-mail or instant messaging, we will save
a copy of the conversation for later reference. If you comment
on our blog, we will save your IP address.
INFORMATION SHARING
Solo does not hand over personal information to third parties or
use it in any non-related matter, as long as we do not have your
written permission to do so (e.g. per e-mail) or are forced to do
so by law.
COOKIES
Solo uses cookies – small files containing a string of characters.
We use cookies to improve the quality and usability of our service.
Most of the cookies used by Solo are so-called session cookies:
they will be deleted after your session automatically. Solo also
uses cookies to identify a user during a session, so the user does
not have to log in on any personalized site again and again.
You can force your browser to block cookies in your browser
settings, but we do not recommend that: some features might
not be usable anymore.
